= kissasia.co =
THE ORDINARY JACKPOT
We live within time.
Time doesn't discriminate
between the rich and poor
the good and evil
or the young and the old.
Time passes equally for everyone.
I live the time I'm given.
Today passes just like yesterday
and tomorrow will be no different.
Today, as always
time passes us by
so indifferently.
EPISODE 1: GOOD THINGS COME
TO THOSE WHO WAIT
Good morning, Mr. Gong.
Morning, Ji-hye.
- Morning.
- You just got here?
Yes, I ran a bit late.
Times have changed.
Good morning, everyone.
Hi, Gong.
Good morning, Mr. Gong.
- Morning, Gi-tae.
- Hi.
- When did you get here?
- Five minutes ago.
Hello, good morning.
- You feel okay this morning?
- I'm totally fine.
- Hello, Mr. Jeong.
- Hi.
Hello, Mr. Yang.
- Hello.
- Good morning.
- Good morning, Mr. Yang.
- Hey, Ju-hui.
- Good morning.
What happened to the outlet manager
who kicked up a fuss?
- How did you know?
- I know everything.
You can run,
but you can't hide from me.
Let's start the meeting.
- Okay.
- Sure.
Mr. Yang, it's time for our meeting.
- Coffee?
- Pardon? Well...
I think you should come over now.
Can I at least get a coffee
to survive the day?
- Fine, I'm coming.
- Good.
I'm coming.
I'll be quick so we can get to work.
- Okay.
Any updates on the discrepancy
between the distribution
and what the mall got?
The mall staff forgot to count
a box they had in storage.
The numbers add up now.
They won't, though.
They still resort to borrowing stock
from other stores
if the numbers don't add up.
You should conduct a spot inspection.
Okay, I'll do that.
Why don't we let it drop this time?
It's obvious they borrowed stock
from another store.
Pointing that out
will only ruffle feathers.
Once sales stabilize
we can check all the remaining stock.
Let's do that, then.
I'll revise the schedule
to reflect that.
Each brand's
projected spring, summer lineup.
I'd like the full list this week.
Can it be done?
- Mr. Yang.
- I'll tell you when it's ready.
We need the list by this week
so we can review it internally
before we place the orders next week.
There's a limit
to what's within my control.
Still, check with the brands for me.
Okay.
- Ji-hye.
- Yes?
Some brands are changing their CI.
Share the drafts with me
and compile a questionnaire
to collect input for a future report.
Can you do that by today?
Yes, I can.
Let me know if it's too much.
I'll help.
Not at all. I can manage.
There's also concern that employees
are managing their time too freely.
The work we do
makes it impossible to work
exactly from nine to six
but I'd like you to follow
company rules as best you can.
- Do you all understand?
- Yes.
Yes.
- Let's get to work, then.
- Okay.
Goodness...
You never get a break, do you?
You can train and mentor the juniors
but you have one troublemaker
of an assistant manager.
Mr. Yang must have
struggles of his own.
It can't be easy
working under a younger guy.
True. It's tough on both of you.
What's this meeting about?
I have no idea
what the higher-ups are thinking.
Oh, shoot.
Where are you going?
- It's my leg day.
- What do you mean?
Let's take the stairs.
RESERVATIONS
FOR 4TH-FLOOR CONFERENCE ROOM
Hello.
- Mr. Jeong?
- Yes?
Am I a zombie, or are you a rat?
What do you mean?
Why did you take the stairs
when the elevator
was working just fine?
Oh, you saw us?
Mr. Gong and I had
something to discuss.
I wonder if you're still ticked off
because I rejected
a few of your ideas.
Did you reject a few ideas?
Why don't I remember that?
Did he?
- Hello, sir.
- You're all here.
- Yes.
- You can sit.
- Thanks.
Okay.
Did you talk to your teams
about managing their time?
- Yes.
Someone will get caught first.
Don't let that be you.
I can't cover for you then.
- Okay.
Let's get things started.
Today's agenda is very simple.
Laknes.
What do you all think about it?
Shall we go clockwise?
Or play rock-paper-scissors?
Their designs are one thing,
but their prices are extremely high.
They're not that well-known
and have a small collection.
And they don't have
that many patterns, either.
I believe
it's a hard brand to launch.
What else?
I believe they just exited
the Korean market.
Unless they've changed
their designs or pricing
won't the result be the same
if we bring them back?
Their designs were hard
to swallow at first.
But times have changed.
They didn't exit
because they flopped.
I think they even got
into the top ten of luxury brands.
Didn't they reach ninth?
Yes, just once.
I get what you're all worried about.
We must do this.
It's our director's order.
Don't take it. Fight back.
Laknes is known
for its radical designs.
Why don't you take it, Mr. Gong?
You're the youngest here
and have the best eye for aesthetics.
No?
As you know, my team doesn't have
the time or bandwidth.
We're the smallest team,
but we handle the most brands.
What do the others think?
Well...
The truth is,
every team is stretched thin.
The team best-suited for the job
would be Mr. Gong's.
You think so too?
I mean, you all have a point
but I fear you're giving him too much
because he's the youngest.
Then Team 4 should take it.
That's not what I meant.
- Mr. Gong.
- Yes?
How about you take Laknes
and give a few brands
to some other teams here?
Can you do it, then?
Yes.
Then we can do it.
Stupid, I told you not to take it.
You're out of your mind.
Why did you give in
when I told you not to?
- Whatever.
- Hey.
If that's not what you meant,
what did you mean?
I tried to defend you
because they all wanted you to...
Gong, can I have a word?
Before you hand over
some of your brands
can you talk to me first?
Yes, of course.
- Let's have a drink soon.
- Sure.
Mr. Kim.
What's this?
It got returned.
Give it to your wife.
Oh, it's a scarf.
Do you think Laknes will work?
Of course not.
We're bringing back a brand
that flopped with zero changes.
Isn't it a jerk move to dump
a sure-fire flop on another team?
I can only go along
with what Mr. Jang suggests.
What else can I do?
You're way too ambitious.
Why don't you give me something too?
What?
You want something of mine?
Well, Mr. Jang is in my corner,
but the director is neutral.
I don't feel safe.
If Mr. Son gets something
from Mr. Jeong
we'll all be in trouble.
Let's plan long-term.
Give me something good, okay?
Thanks for the scarf.
Everyone's dead anxious.
Laknes is a done deal
because the director wants it
but you're the only one
who'll do it without complaint.
They want Kim as associate director,
but his sales aren't good enough
so they're taking a few
of your brands to boost his numbers.
And now Son is worried
he won't get promoted this time.
And people think I don't care at all
who you give those brands to.
Should I give you one too
if you're that upset?
I'm just worried for the two of us.
Don't give me anything.
Here's how I feel.
I want my brands to do better
at the new teams.
It's like I want them to meet
a good adoptive family.
Instead of letting them
take what's yours
why don't you take a stand?
"I can't take Laknes.
Let me secure my own sales."
Even I think
only I can handle Laknes.
You don't want it, either.
Exactly, I don't even want to do it,
so why would you?
Since we're on the topic,
think of your poor team.
They take all the brands no one wants
and do all the hard work.
Once the brands are on track,
they give them to someone else.
What the heck is that?
Are you consoling me or what?
I feel sorry for you, that's all.
I really do.
To be honest, no one cares about me
but aren't you in Mr. Jang's camp?
What's up with him?
He should be responsible
for the employee he promoted.
Why are you always suffering?
Don't you think... What the heck?
Gosh, that punk.
Wait up.
- You're leaving?
- Yes.
Bye.
- Take care, Gong.
- Bye.
I'm heading out.
Sure, bye.
Wow, I'm starving.
Let's eat. What do you want?
How about the barbecue place
we went to last time?
That place is too cheap,
and you're buying.
Oh, am I buying?
Will you join us, Mr. Gong?
No, I'm fine.
Okay, I'll head home, then.
I'm leaving too, sir.
- Let's have what Ji-hye wants.
- Ji-hye?
What I want?
She prefers pork.
- She likes pork?
- Yes.
Then we should go for somaek.
- Somaek.
- Are we getting drunk again?
Oh, sounds good.
TRAIN IS APPROACHING
STOP
What did the doctor say?
About your father.
Oh, that? He got a few tests done.
The results aren't out yet.
But they said
it's nothing to worry about.
Still, keep an eye on him.
Older people aren't like
what you think.
Okay, I'll do that.
Tell me when you get the results.
I can put you in touch
with a different hospital.
You'd do that?
Thank you.
Are you busy, Ji-hye?
No.
Can you work the tongs, then?
Oh, let me.
I don't mind cooking the meat.
Why? Is it because she's a woman?
Or because she's a contract worker?
No, it's not exactly that...
Man or woman, contract or full-time,
Ji-hye is still family.
Aren't you the youngest?
Yes, I am. I should've
watched the grill. Sorry.
I don't know what Gong's thinking
but I don't plan to let her go
after her contract expires.
- What?
- Just you wait.
I brown-nose everyone
I see at work for a reason.
I'm trying to secure an opening.
I grovel and beg, just for you.
I see. Thank you, Mr. Yang.
If you're grateful,
flip the meat before it burns.
Sorry.
Let's drink.
You have a great posture, Mr. Gong.
Don't most office workers
get tech-neck and crooked spines
after seven years?
I have dry eyes and fatty liver,
and that's bad enough for me.
You stayed late.
This is early for me.
You look good.
I pretend to be good.
Are you going home?
I have plans.
Let's get a drink.
Let's have pufferfish soup
and split the bill.
I have plans, I said.
You don't have plans.
Hurry up.
CHEONGJIN PUFFERFISH
Ma'am, can we get another bottle?
- Thank you.
Hey, why are you always alone?
Other team leaders are
always with their minions.
Your team leader
doesn't take you anywhere.
I bet it's the same reason.
Exactly.
I'm asking
since I'm just a member of a team
but you're a team leader.
The head of Legal is equivalent
to a managing director
so to be exact, you're above me.
Can you just not?
You treated
everyone from our year to beef
because you made team leader.
But you're an outcast
in your own team.
You're always
out and about on your own.
What was that brand called? Laknes?
Why are you letting everyone
play you like a fiddle?
What's the point
of being a team leader?
The company has
a big picture for Laknes.
I happen to be
in charge of the backdrop.
Okay. Let's say that
about the company's big picture.
Why is Mr. Yang drawing the picture
for your team?
He's always out
with the two underlings.
He's making you do all the work
while he plays team leader.
I know he joined Hongsung before you
but isn't that just wrong?
Mr. Yang...
- He gets on my nerves.
- Right?
But part of me thinks
even if he gets on my nerves
and plays team leader
if he hits our goals
and make things work,
isn't that good enough?
We're all there to do a job.
Is it all fine if things work out?
You suffer.
If my suffering means things work out
it's all good.
Is Hongsung a company or a temple?
You might actually reach nirvana.
See you. Take care at work.
You're still talking about work?
That's all you talk about.
Is your workday not over yet?
Jeez, Gong Eun-tae.
Take care.
What kind of life am I living?
- Are you all right?
- Yes.
- Let me help.
- No, leave it.
I was born into a family
that wasn't rich,
but wasn't poor, either.
I could climb if I worked hard
and I could fall
if I made one mistake.
GONG EUN-TAE
That's why I studied hard.
I wanted to get
into a better college...
and I wanted to get a better job.
Regardless of the result,
working hard put me at ease.
That's what made me think
I was living life well.
That's how I got a job
at Hongsung International.
They have the second-most turnover
and the third most brands
in the industry.
It's a large company
with 900 employees
and annual sales of 800 billion won.
My parents didn't know
the name of the company
but they were proud
I worked at a large one.
And I was grateful I could
support myself before I was too old.
Nothing changed
after I started working.
I remained in the same frame
spending the same amount of time
and did my best as always.
For three whole years
I was the first to come in
and the last to leave.
So I got promoted
to assistant manager.
Three more years of that,
and I made team leader.
After all those years of work
I can afford an efficiency apartment
a slightly fatty liver, dry eyes
and an almost slipped disk.
Does everyone live like this?
If I work a little harder
will my life become a little better?
For what did I live and work so hard?
And when did I stop
living and working so hard?
- Who is it?
- Hey.
- Oh, hello.
- Hello.
- I brought your dry-cleaning.
- Thank you.
Oh, one more thing.
I lost one of your dress shirts.
- Did you?
- Yes.
Which one did you lose?
My wife only said it's in the ledger,
but she can't find it.
I don't know which one it is.
Then I guess...
Have a good evening.
And since when did I stop
getting angry?
HANKYEONG BANK
EULJIRO 1-GA STATION
Mr. Yang.
Hi, Ju-hui.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
Why are you so down this morning?
It's weird to be excited about work.
Beware of such people.
Are you worried
about the brand shift?
The brand shift? What do you mean?
You haven't heard?
- Morning.
- Hello.
Good morning.
- Mr. Yang.
- Hello.
- Morning. Can you...
- Let's talk.
What is this about?
What's this about handing over
our brands to other teams?
Stuff happened.
Yes, but why?
We have to launch Laknes.
We have to start from scratch
and it'll be a lot of work.
So we have to pack up the brands
we were working on
so other teams can take over.
Don't you think that's too much?
None of our previous brands
started off normal.
Eynard?
They made a decent amount,
and Team 3 couldn't handle it.
So they were fine,
but what about the others?
Weren't they all brands
that should've been dropped?
We took them in and revived them
only to lose them.
Now we get Laknes
that flopped once already?
Even if the team leader
doesn't have much clout
that doesn't mean
they can walk all over the team.
Mr. Yang.
Do you think
I want to lose the brands
I was working on?
Mr. Gong.
Can you please do
just one thing for me?
Let us keep our projects.
That's the least you can do
if you expect us to trust you.
Is that so much to ask?
Just let us do our job in peace.
Please?
Did Mr. Yang headbutt you?
That stupid punk.
He was right, though.
A team leader is useless
if he loses his team's trust.
So what? If Yang headbutted you
what will you do?
Shouldn't you headbutt someone too?
Did you ever see me get angry?
Have I seen you get angry?
I haven't.
I don't shout when I'm angry.
If I do, I only have to sort out
that aftermath.
No one cares about that
when they're angry.
They just lash out.
So what? What will you do now?
I must do something.
Like what?
ASSOCIATE DIRECTOR'S OFFICE
- Is he in?
- Yes.
Come in.
What is it?
I have something to say.
- Will it take a while?
- It might.
Sit.
What is it?
It's about Laknes.
Could you give it to another team?
Is your team disheartened
about taking Laknes?
Did Yang Jun-ho complain?
Talk to me.
He's the only subordinate
who would complain.
Everyone agrees, though.
Hey.
Will you let them
control you forever?
If you really can't do it,
then I'll accept that.
I can give it to another team.
But that's not the case.
You can take it,
but one of your lackeys can't.
Isn't that why you took a deep breath
before coming in to see me?
Do you think I made you team leader
to take on easy jobs?
No, I never thought so.
Jeez, that's exactly what you think.
It's easy to keep doing
what you're good at.
As long as your brain works
anyone can do that. However...
It's hard to revive a dying brand.
That's not for just anyone.
I gave you the job
because I believe in you.
Yes, it will be hard work.
And your team will complain,
but what can I do?
They pull off
what you tell them to do.
Bear with it.
And pull it off.
It goes on your record.
Get out of here.
Darn it.
- Gi-tae.
- Yes?
- Let's go out for a smoke.
- Okay.
Ji-hye, join us for some air.
Okay.
Jeez...
PRESSED PORK HEAD MEAT
KOREAN BEEF
SEONGGYEONG BUTCHER
SYSTEM IS DOWN
Sorry, the checkout machine
isn't working.
What should I do, then?
Do you have cash?
Yes.
- Here.
- That's 10,000 won.
We're out of change.
I'll come by another time.
Would you like to buy
a lottery ticket?
Sorry?
Two beers are 5,000 won,
and a ticket is 5,000 won.
- Sure, give me one.
- Okay.
Random numbers?
Okay.
Here you go.
Do I get a plastic bag?
You didn't pay 100 won for one.
MOM
Hello, Mom.
Did you have dinner?
I'm eating right now.
Do you have any food at home?
Should I send you some?
I still have what you sent me
last time.
I sent that a long time ago.
You should eat it up quickly.
Tell me if you ever need
any side dishes.
I'll tell you if I do.
Okay. Oh, there's one more thing.
It's nothing serious.
Can you give your brother
five million won?
What is it this time?
Your brother was on the night shift
and some drunkards got into a fight.
When Eun-seok tried to stop them,
one guy fell and hurt his back.
He's demanding your brother
pay for the treatment
but you know he's penniless.
A security guard barely makes enough
after expenses and his kid's tuition.
I'll give him a call.
No, don't call him.
He doesn't know I called you.
He knows.
I'll call him.
GONG EUN-SEOK
CALLING
MY LITTLE BROTHER
Hey, Eun-tae.
You need money?
Gosh, did Mom tell you?
I told her not to tell you.
Will five million won do?
Yes, that'll be enough.
I'll pay you back soon.
When?
What? When?
When can I pay you back?
Let me see...
Do you know
how much I lent you so far?
Just ask for it.
Why do you say you owe me?
But I should pay you back.
Eun-seok.
Do you think everyone
with an office job can save up?
I don't have much.
Do you know how much it costs
to just live and breathe in Seoul?
We're family, aren't we?
If we can't help each other
let's at least not burden each other.
Okay. Sorry.
- I'll wire it right now.
- Oh, thanks.
TYPE YOUR PIN
5,000,000 WON SENT TO GONG EUN-SEOK
SUPPLEMENT FOR STOMACH LINING
SWOOSH
6 LOTTERY WINNERS THIS WEEK
EACH GETS 1.9 BILLION WON
LOTTO
5609TH DRAWING
CONGRATULATIONS
TOTAL WINNINGS: 1,977,507,240 WON
THE ORDINARY JACKPOT
I've had enough for the day.
Are you going home?
Yes, if I stay any longer,
I feel like I might die.
I feel the same.
Why are you still here?
If I leave now, I'll die tomorrow.
We all live one day at a time.
Wrap it up quickly.
Have a good night.
THIS WEEK'S TASKS
GOT OFF WORK YET?
GONG EUN-TAE
Subtitles by Jennifer Jean Lim